# **CURRICULUM VITAE**

#### CURRICULUM VITAE OF: ALHASSAN ALHASSAN FUSEINI

#### PROFESSIONAL PROFILE

An experienced self-motivated and dedicated individual with outstanding organizational and communication skills, proven ability to develop and implement human resource strategies policies and procedures for effective and efficient use of resources.

Able to work independently and be part of a productive team and multi-tasking abilities required to meet demanding deadlines.

#### **KEY SKILLS AND COMPETENCES**

- **\*** Excellent in influencing and facilitating skills.
- Presentational skills.
- ❖ Ability to develop and implement strategies.
- \* Team player.

#### **PERSONAL INFORMATION**

**Date of Birth**: 12th November, 1982

**Place of Birth**: Tamale

**Nationality:** Ghanaian

**Region:** Northern

**Home Town**: Tamale

Marital Status: Married

Language(S) Spoken: Dagbani and English

**Religion:** Islam

**Home Address:** H/No. CM BLK 'I' 83 Choggu

**Postal Address**: C/O Abubakari Yushawu Box 1 E/R Tamale N/R.

**Contacts:** 0246250633 / 0204508846

Emails: archimedis12@yahoo.com / archimedis12.aaf@gmail.com

# **EDUCATIONAL AND TRAINING HISTORY**

DATE	<u>INSTITUTION</u>	CERTIFICATE OBTAINED
2020 – 2022	C.K. Tedam University of Technology and	Master of Philosophy in Mathematics
	Applied Sciences, Navrongo	Education
2016 – 2017	University of Cape Coast	Master of Education in Mathematics
2009 – 2011	Institute For Educational Development And	Bachelor Degree of Education (Basic)
	Extension, University of Education, Winneba	
2004 - 2007	Tamale College of Education	Diploma in Basic Education (DBE)
2001 – 2003	Tamale Islamic Science Senior High	SSSCE in General Science
1998 – 2000	Choggu Nuri Islam Junior High	BECE

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

From September, 2006 to July, 2007: Choggu Demonstration Junior High (Out-Programme)

Work: Mathematics Teacher

❖ From 2007 to August, 2014: Kplinyin D/A Junior High School

Work: Mathematics Teacher

❖ September, 2014 to Date: Kumbungu District Education Office

Office Held: Examinations Officer

## **LEADERSHIP EXPERIENCE**

<b>DATE</b>	INSTITUTION/ORGANIZATION	<b>POSITION</b>
1998 - 2000	Choggu Nuri Islam JHS	Class Prefect
2002 - 2003	Tamale Islamic Science SHS	Nkrumah House Prefect
2005 - 2006	Tamale College of Education	Kaleem House Prefect
2013 - 2019	Alumni Union of TISSEC	Former Vice President

## **COMPUTER SKILLS**

# Knowledge in the Following:

- Microsoft Word
- **❖** Microsoft Excel
- Microsoft Access
- Microsoft Power Point

#### **PERSONAL ATTRIBUTES**

- ❖ A quick learner willing to confront and learn new technology.
- **Experience** in building strong rapport with co-workers.
- Flexible and able to adapt quickly and pragmatic to changes.
- \* Ready to be corrected and to work under pressure.

## **INTEREST AND ACTIVITIES**

- Calculations
- Watching football matches and athletics

## **REFERENCES**

Chief Alhassan Imoro

Former Laboratory Technician

Tamale College of Education

Contact: 0207832475

Mr. Zakaria Abubakari Sadiq

Former Head of Mathematics Department

Tamale College of Education

Contacts: 0208408044 / 0244436351